[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You can kill a butterfly if you hold its wings.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Mekhi Phifers character in the movie Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "Derek", "incorrect_answers": ["Chris", "Sean", "Greg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Dog Day Afternoon, it was stated that Sonny was sentenced to how many years in prison for holding up the bank?", "correct_answer": "20 Years", "incorrect_answers": ["40 Years", "10 Years", "Life Imprisonment"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the study of atmospheric dust and its effect on life on Earth?", "correct_answer": "coniology", "incorrect_answers": ["lithology", "tricology", "vexillogy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement concerning Slovakia and Slovenia is true?", "correct_answer": "Slovenia has access to the Adriatic Sea.", "incorrect_answers": ["Both countries have access to the Black Sea.", "Slovakia has access to the Baltic Sea.", "Both countries are landlocked."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most likely suffix of the email address of someone who is Dutch?", "correct_answer": ".nl", "incorrect_answers": [".hl", ".ho", ".du"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Dirty Dancing character said, Shes with me. She came with me.?", "correct_answer": "Billy", "incorrect_answers": ["Robbie", "Neil", "Johnny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the largest city and capital of Sweden?", "correct_answer": "Stockholm", "incorrect_answers": ["Helsinki", "Oslo", "Gothenburg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who developed the process of conching, which is used for a better refining of chocolate?", "correct_answer": "Rudolph Lindt", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "The Cadbury brothers", "Milton Hershey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the iPod introduced?", "correct_answer": "2001", "incorrect_answers": ["2003", "2008", "2007"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Asias most densely populated country which has about three million people and an area of less than 250 square miles (402 km\u00b2).", "correct_answer": "Singapore", "incorrect_answers": ["Hokkaido", "Taiwan", "Laos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These lines can be heard in what 1964 movie starring Sean Connery?\nMei-Lei: Can I do anything for you, Mr. Bond? \nJames Bond: Uh, just a drink. A martini, shaken, not stirred.", "correct_answer": "Goldfinger", "incorrect_answers": ["Thunderball", "The Man with the Golden Gun", "Quantum of Solace"]}]